ROHIT SATPATHY

Senior Associate

Address Jamshedpur, India 831003

Phone +91 7909069877

E-mail Rohit.satpathy27@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rohit-

satpathy-498029b



I am a seasoned SAP SD consultant with a career span of 6 years (3 YRS SAP SD ECC and 3 YRS SAP S4 Hana), which has exposed me to diverse operating modules, Landscapes and scenarios. The 6 years of experience includes 1 complete end to end domestic implementation, 1 development/roll out project, 1 support. I am currently working in a global implementation project where in we are implementing S/4 hana for APAC, EMENA and AMERICA business region of the company.

Skills

Sap S/4 Hana Sales & Distribution	Advanced
Pricing sales	Upper intermediate
Advanced ATP	Intermediate
Microsoft excel/word/office	Advanced
JIRA (Project management tool)	Advanced
Leadership capability	Upper intermediate
Creative problem solving	Advanced
Master data migration	Upper intermediate
Integration	Intermediate

Work History

2022-06 - Current

Senior Associate

PwC AC, Acceleration center, BENGALURU

• Achieved client satisfaction and loyalty by establishing collaborative relationships, facilitating needs assessment.

- Worked on integration processes, Utilizing the standard SAP out of the box offering, APIs for integration objects such as customer, products, Sales order (create/change/Read), delivery notification etc.
- Actively participated in the business workshops to gather the business requirements and document them in key design documents
- Responsible for preparing the business functional specific documents, Configuration documents and integration mapping documents
- Worked on the latest S/4 offerings such as advanced ATP (PAL, PAC and BOP), advanced returns for returns and claims process, Condition contracts for Rebates, Business partner, and Credit management

2021-05 - 2022-06 **Associate**

PwC AC, Acceleration center, BENGALURU

- CLIENT CROSBY (US, MATERIAL HANDLING INDUSTRY) JUNE'21, CURRENT (IMPLEMENTATION)
- Leading the master data track for all the OTC objects (customer, MM (sales), CMIR, customer hierarchy, pricing condition records etc.)
- Working along with snaplogic (3rd party tool) team to extract, transform and cleanse legacy data
- Working along with client for their legacy data and requirements
- Utilizing master data migration tools such as LSMW, LTMC and tool based on standard BAPI and FM
- Master data design documentation to capture the relevant requirement
- Integration with other modules such as MM, FI and EWM
- Master data cutover plan and load

2021-06 - 2021-12 **Associate**

PwC AC, Acceleration center Bangalore, BENGALURU

- Lead the otc master data track (especially customer and material master sales)
- The migration was from SAP ECC to S/4 (currently operating in 4 regions APAC, US, EMENA, and RSA)
- We were responsible for conducting the regional workshop to collect regional data and suggest global data for a single S4 system for all regions
- We were utilizing MDG environment as the central infrastructure
- Working in phases, as followed in agile methodology, I was also involved in the development of implementation plan for the next phase of implementation

2019-11 - 2021-05 Software Engineer

Accenture Solution Pvt. Ltd, BENGALURU

- I was one of the active SAP SD member right from the blue printing stage till the go-live phase
- Responsible for creating blue print document, sample process design in sandbox, process design and UAT, master data creation and load, go-live and hyper care support
- Worked on niche SD processes such as intercompany transactions, 3rd party scenario, MTO processes, smartforms, and credit management

- Tool development through LSMW
- LTMC, or BDC for data
- Supporting and learning other business modules like MM, EWM and FI
- FIORI report development for sales reporting and analysis.

2016-12 - 2019-11 **Associate Software Engineer**

Accenture Solution Pvt. Ltd., BENGALURU

 CLIENT - ANHEUSER-BUSCH INBEV {BEVERAGES} (US) (DEVELOPMENT/ROLL OUT) (APRIL'17 TO MARCH'19)

CHENT _ DEITED (HS) (DUADAA)
enhancements, pricing procedure and shipping & route determination
sales order type
☐ Worked extensively on the business smartforms, output determinations,
☐ Preparation of proposal document, estimation delivery plans
$\hfill\square$ Enhancement of various regions was carried under change requests (CR)

enhancements, pricing procedure and shipping & route determination	í
CLIENT - PFIZER (US) {PHARMA}	
□ Providing production support and solving end-user problems.	
☐ Analyzing the incidents and tickets and providing permanent solution	ns.
☐ Working on P1, P2, P3 & P4 incidents based on the criticality and serving	ice
request within SLA.	
☐ Pre-sales activities such as inquiry, quotation and major business acti	vitie
such as pricing,	
billing, shipments, ATP, credit management, EDI and IDOCS, output	
determination among the	
others	

Education

2012-01 - 2016-01 **B-TECH: MECHANICAL**

VELLORE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - Vellore, Tamil Nadu

GPA: 9.02

2011-06 - 2012-06 **High School Degree: Science**

JAMSHEDPUR PUBLIC SCHOOL - Jamshedpur

Percentage - 84.4 %

2009-06 - 2010-06 **SECONDARY**

JAMSHEDPUR PUBLIC SCHOOL

GPA: 9.6

Accomplishments

- Working with Accenture I have received star of the month award for my contribution in implementing mass pricing upload tool for business
- Working with PwC AC, I have received recognition for my contribution in handling the client on the major master data migration

Languages

English
Advanced
Hindi
Advanced
French
Beginner

Certifications

2022-07 Scrum master certification